

MD SAQUIB SHAKEEL

WEB DEVELOPER

+91 773 935 1707

Okhla village, Jamia Nagar, New Delhi, India

saquib.shakeel.1866@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: <u>@saquibshakeel</u>

https://github.com/SaquibShakeel

ABOUT

I'm pursuing my B.Tech in Electrical Engineering (2nd year) from Jamia Millia Islamia, New Delhi.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

I've worked with various types of projects on frontend development and have mastered multiple programming languages. Currently on the road to mastering React.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

JAMIA MILLIA ISLAMIA, NEW DELHI

B.TECH ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING | 2020 - PRESENT

ST. MICHAEL'S HIGH SCHOOL

12th GRADE - CBSE | 2019

Scored 87%

KENDRIYA VIDYALAYA DANAPUR CANTT

10th GRADE - CBSE | 2017

Scored 10 cgpa

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER

IEEE COMPUTER SOCIETY JMI - STUDENT CHAPTER | FEB 2022 - PRESENT

HEAD OF EVENTS

IEEE COMPUTER SOCIETY JMI - STUDENT CHAPTER | JUL 2021 - JAN 2022

SKILLS

- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- MySQL
- Java
- JavaScript

- HTML
- Python (Programming Language)
- Robot Operating System (ROS)
- OpenCV